<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">The Great Gatsby</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Chapter 1</string>
    <string name="article_text">
        <b>In the summer of 1922,</b> Nick writes, he had just arrived in New York, where he moved to work in the bond business, and rented a house on
        a part of Long Island called West Egg. Unlike the conservative, aristocratic East Egg, West Egg is home to the “new rich,” those who,
        having made their fortunes recently, have neither the social connections nor the refinement to move among the East Egg set. West Egg is
        characterized by lavish displays of wealth and garish poor taste. Nick’s comparatively modest West Egg house is next door to Gatsby’s
        mansion, a sprawling Gothic monstrosity.\n\n
        Nick is unlike his West Egg neighbors;<web><b><i> www.google.com </i></b></web> whereas they lack social connections and aristocratic pedigrees,
        Nick graduated from Yale and has many connections on East Egg. One night, he drives out to East Egg to have dinner with his cousin Daisy and her husband,
        Tom Buchanan,
        a former member of Nick’s social club at Yale. Tom, a powerful figure dressed in riding clothes, greets Nick on the porch. Inside, Daisy
        lounges on a couch with her friend Jordan Baker, a competitive golfer who yawns as though bored by her surroundings.\n\n
        Tom tries to interest the others in a book called The Rise of the Colored Empires by a man named Goddard. The book espouses racist,
        white-supremacist attitudes that Tom seems to find convincing. Daisy teases Tom about the book but is interrupted when Tom leaves the
        room to take a phone call. Daisy follows him hurriedly, and Jordan tells Nick that the call is from Tom’s lover in New York.\n\n
        Nick Carraway’s perceptions and attitudes regarding the events and characters of the novel are central to The Great Gatsby. Writing the
        novel is Nick’s way of grappling with the meaning of a story in which he played a part. The first pages of Chapter 1 establish certain
        contradictions in Nick’s point of view. Although he describes himself as tolerant and nonjudgmental, he also views himself as morally
        privileged, having a better sense of “decencies” than most other people. While Nick has a strong negative reaction to his experiences in
        New York and eventually returns to the Midwest in search of a less morally ambiguous environment, even during his initial phase of
        disgust, Gatsby stands out for him as an exception. Nick admires Gatsby highly, despite the fact that Gatsby represents everything Nick
        scorns about New York. Gatsby clearly poses a challenge to Nick’s customary ways of thinking about the world, and Nick’s struggle to
        come to terms with that challenge inflects everything in the novel.
    </string>
    <string name="add_comment" >Add Comment</string>

</resources>