<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoActivitiesChallange</string>
    <string name="button1">Button1</string>
    <string name="button2">Button2</string>
    <string name="button3">Button3</string>

    <string name="displayText_one">Marie Curie, née Maria Sklodowska, was born in Warsaw on November 7, 1867, the daughter of a
        secondary-school teacher. She received a general education in local schools and some scientific training from her father.
        She became involved in a students’ revolutionary organization and found it prudent to leave Warsaw, then in the part of Poland
        dominated by Russia, for Cracow, which at that time was under Austrian rule. In 1891, she went to Paris to continue her studies
        at the Sorbonne where she obtained Licenciateships in Physics and the Mathematical Sciences. She met Pierre Curie, Professor in the
        School of Physics in 1894 and in the following year they were married. She succeeded her husband as Head of the Physics Laboratory at
        the Sorbonne, gained her Doctor of Science degree in 1903, and following the tragic death of Pierre Curie in 1906, she took his place
        Professor of General Physics in the Faculty of Sciences, the first time a woman had held this position. She was also appointed Director of
        the Curie Laboratory in the Radium Institute of the University of Paris, founded in 1914.</string>

    <string name="displayText_two">Albert Einstein was born at Ulm, in Württemberg, Germany, on March 14, 1879. Six weeks later the family moved to Munich,
        where he later on began his schooling at the Luitpold Gymnasium. Later, they moved to Italy and Albert continued his education at Aarau,
        Switzerland and in 1896 he entered the Swiss Federal Polytechnic School in Zurich to be trained as a teacher in physics and mathematics.
        In 1901, the year he gained his diploma, he acquired Swiss citizenship and, as he was unable to find a teaching post, he accepted a position as
        technical assistant in the Swiss Patent Office. In 1905 he obtained his doctor’s degree.</string>

    <string name="displayText_three">Charles Darwin, in full Charles Robert Darwin, (born February 12, 1809, Shrewsbury, Shropshire, England—died April 19,
        1882, Downe, Kent), English naturalist whose scientific theory of evolution by natural selection became the foundation of modern evolutionary
        studies. An affable country gentleman, Darwin at first shocked religious Victorian society by suggesting that animals and humans shared a common
        ancestry. However, his nonreligious biology appealed to the rising class of professional scientists, and by the time of his death evolutionary
        imagery had spread through all of science, literature, and politics. Darwin, himself an agnostic, was accorded the ultimate British accolade of
        burial in Westminster Abbey, London.

        Darwin formulated his bold theory in private in 1837–39, after returning from a voyage around the world aboard HMS Beagle, but it was not until
        two decades later that he finally gave it full public expression in On the Origin of Species (1859), a book that has deeply influenced modern
        Western society and thought.</string>
</resources>