<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollingText Homework</string>
    <string name="article_title">Pele</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Pele : BIOGRAPHY</string>
    <string name="article_text">Brazilian football (soccer) player, in his time probably the most famous and possibly the best-paid athlete in the world.
        He was part of the Brazilian national teams that won three World Cup championships  https://www.britannica.com/biography/Pele-Brazilian-athlete
\n\n
After playing for a minor league club at Bauru, São Paulo state, Pelé (whose nickname apparently is without significance) was rejected by major club teams in the city of São Paulo.
\n\n
<b>Childhood:</b>
\n\n
<b><i>Birth Date</i></b> In 1956, however, he joined the Santos Football Club, which, with Pelé at inside left forward,
        won nine São Paulo league championships and, in 1962 and 1963, both the Libertadores Cup and the Intercontinental Club Cup.
        Sometimes called “Pérola Negra” (“Black Pearl”), he became a Brazilian national hero. He combined kicking power and accuracy with a
        remarkable ability to anticipate other players’ moves. After the 1958 World Cup, Pelé was declared a national treasure by the Brazilian
        government in order to ward off large offers from European clubs and ensure that he would remain in Brazil. On November 19, 1969,
        in his 909th first-class match, he scored his 1,000th goal.
\n\n
<b><i>Childhood</i></b>Pele is a legendary sporting figure and an iconic soccer player who during his active years ruled the game to the point of
        being called the ‘King of Football’. Till date, he is widely regarded by football fans, critics, experts and players (current and retired)
        as the best player of all time. With his impeccable style, electrifying play and impressive performance, he scored a total of 1281 goals in
        1363 games. It was his deep embedded penchant for the game and knack for scoring spectacular goals that made him a star around the world.
        He was praised for his exceptional heading ability, powerful shot and unbowed goal scoring. A Brazilian national team footballer and key player
        for the Santos club, he played a major role in every game he played. While at field, he gave his hundred per cent to every match and played
        like an unbeaten pro since his very first professional game. Over his career that spanned for a little over two decades, he showcased some
        invincible performances and catapulted the popularity of the game astronomically. Other than his spectacular showmanship on the field, Pele
        is regarded as the ultimate humanitarian as well, for he has raised his voice to enhance the living standard and social conditions of the poor,
        a number of times. In his active years, he created numerous records, some of which till date remain undefeated and unaltered. To know more
        about this celebrated footballer, scroll further.
        \n\n
</string>
</resources>